welcome to the internet explorer is that
party a 27 years old internet explorer
is finally retiring and its final
resting place can be found here in south
korea as it says on the gravestone made
by a south korean developer internet
explorer will be remembered by the best
tool to download other browsers to
celebrate the retirement of internet
explorer on today's video we are going
to take a look at some browsers that are
not internet explorer and that many of
you might have not heard of until today
we're going to look at browsers made
only for gamers or only for web
developers browsers focused only on
productivity and even browsers without
taps
opera gx is a browser made for gamers
and is one of the coolest looking
browsers i have ever tried it has tons
of features built around gaming
it comes with something called the gx
corner which is a tab where we can find
free games games on sale a game release
calendar gaming news a new game trailers
it lets us limit how much bandwidth cpu
and ram the browser can use it has
twitch and discord integrated on the
sidebar as well as telegram whatsapp and
facebook messenger it also has a player
tab to connect to apple music spotify
and youtube music as well it comes with
something called pin boards where we can
save organize and share links from all
around the web the colors can be
customized it has very cool looking
things and we can even add sound effects
when we type on the keyboard or when our
mouse is on top of a button or when we
click something and it comes with a vpn
and an ad blocker included and because
it's based on chromium you can install
any chrome extension like you normally
would
lte browser is a browser i did not know
i needed until i tried it out it's a
browser specifically made to build debug
and test mobile websites it allows us to
test our website in a variety of devices
with different screen sizes from phones
to tablets laptops and desktops we can
test in two devices at the same time we
can add our own devices and we can also
record a video of the testing session if
we need to when testing in two devices
the interactions are synchronized which
makes testing so much easier it can also
simulate slow connections so we can see
how our website will load in a phone
with bad internet and it also generates
lighthouse performance reports
it also allows us to take and edit
screenshots of box on our website to
share them with our team before we keep
going i want to remind you that if you
want to learn to code and you want to do
it for free with me and in hangul then
please click the link below there you
will find free courses on many many
things from javascript to react react
native go python redox graphql many many
things for free with me click the link
below and i will see you there
firefox developer edition is also a
browser targeted towards developers it
has the
best debugger for css grid i have ever
seen it's absolutely fantastic it's
great it also has a killer font panel
that i'm sure many of us have needed
before and a very nice css debugger for
inactive css code that explains why the
css is not being applied to an element
it also comes with a world-class
javascript debugger that i think
deserves its own video
sidekiq and sigma os are two browsers
that focus on productivity sidekick
allows us to install the work apps that
we use the most in our sidebar we can
also be logged in multiple accounts of
the same website at the same time we can
use their beautiful search bar to search
across apps tabs and our browsing
history and something that i think it's
pretty cool is that it allows us to
organize our tabs in sessions so we can
have a group of tabs that we open when
it's work time other group when we do
shopping and other one we want to have
fun and we want to kill some time sigma
always is very similar to sidekick it
has a very nice search bar and it allows
you to organize your tabs in workspaces
it syncs across multiple devices it also
supports a split screen and it has a
very cool keyboard shortcuts for even
more productivity
stack is a very ambitious browser they
have a team of 13 people working there
and they raised more than 2 million
dollars stack does not have tabs instead
websites are open next to each other in
cards you can make groups of cards for
different moments in your day for work
you can create a stack that has your
email your calendar and slack next to
each other or for study you can create a
stack that has youtube and notion
together all these browsers sidekiq
sigma os and stack have something in
common and that is that they are free up
to a point if you want to have more
workspaces or sync across devices or add
more apps to your sidebar you're going
to have to pay around eight dollars per
month
but now there's something i would like
to know and that is from today's video
which browser picked your interest the
most which one are you going to download
which one are you going to test and also
would you pay for a browser because we
are used to using browsers for free
brave browser google chrome neighbor
whale but maybe we should pay for a
browser because if we don't pay for
something with money we're paying for
something with our data so let me know
what do you think in the comments for me
personally i really like the lte browser
i have been using it for a while and
it's great to test browsers in every
mobile device is just amazing and also
the opera gaming one it looks super
super sweet let me know the answer to
these questions in the comments i'm
gonna be looking at them right now thank
you as always for watching if you like
this channel if you want to support the
content please leave a like and
subscribe it's two links is for free for
you but it helps us a lot thank you so
much for watching stay free stay happy
eat kimchi i'm samidah salaam heyo see
you on the next one bye